

Lakisha Adu

- <u> lakishaadu@yahoo.de</u>
- in linkedin.com/in/lakisha-adu/
- github.com/lakishaadu

I am an analytics-oriented marketer with recent experience from a 15-week analytics bootcamp. I love applying my new knowledge and contributing to the success of campaigns. I have a high level of comprehension and am a quick learner. Managing multiple projects with tight deadlines is no problem for me.

Work experience

- Marketing Manager | JITpay Group
 11/2022 03/2023
 Managed marketing for customer & employee acquisition.
 Organized and planned events.
- Content-Marketing Manager | KUPPER IT GmbH 04/2022 - 09/2022
 Developed content for marketing materials.
 Planned and implemented content strategies to increase brand awareness, drive traffic, and generate leads.
- 04/2020 10/2021
 Developed B2B sales marketing activities;
 Focused on sales and lead generation, consistently driving revenue growth and customer acquisition;

Marketing & Support | Wehner Consulting GmbH

- Seminarmanager | MST Group GmbH 05/2018 - 08/2020
 Planned and coordinated seminars for personnel development at the BMW Training Center and MAN;
- Event Manager | Seminarcenter IM EINKLANG 07/2017 - 04/2018
 Maintained the Home and Facebook pages;
 Managed Meta Ads and Marketing Campaign;
 Conceptualized creative event concepts;

Soft Skills & Languages

Soft Skills

Hands-on Person Analytic thinker Problem solving Communication Skills

Language English: B2 Spanish: A1 German: Native

Education

- Marketing Analytics | WBS Coding School, Berlin Since 04/2023 - 08/2023 | Hybrid Further Education Focus: Tracking, Measurement, Analysis, Reporting;
- Communication & Event Management | IST Hochschule f. Management, Düsseldorf
 Since 04/2021 - today | Bachelor of Arts | Part-time
 Focus: Brand Management, Business Administration;
- Event Manager | IST Studieninstitut, Düsseldorf
 02/2019 02/2021 | Hybrid Further Education | Part-time
 Focus: Venue Selection and Logistics, Event Production;
- Event Manager | TNC Group GmbH, Leipzig
 09/2014 06/2017 | Apprenticeship
 Focus: Project Management, Promotion, Social Media;

Tech Skills & Knowledge

Digital Marketing

Digital Marketing Fundamentals Google Tag Manager | Google Analytics Hotjar (Heatmap and user behavior analysis)

Web Development

HTML | CSS | JavaScript (Frontend)
SQL (Database query language)
BigQuery (Data warehouse and analytics)

Conversion Optimization:

A/B Testing (For conversion rate optimization) Looker Studio (Data visualization & analytics) Web Usability & Conversion-Centered Design

Graphic Design:

Canva (Graphic design) Photoshop (Image editing)